{
    "id": "06a4ff0c943f47fba4e639e97e23ab82",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Do you know …………………………. has happened?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ea0a2385510446018edad05701168455"
        },
        {
            "question": "He always preaches …………………………………….. he never practices.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "01a3452448674b00860c28a9f4e5a174"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the book …………………………………… I lent you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "96bc4fffc6e549ab8c25f8e887cbb869"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has no sword with ………………………………. to fight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8517b94c7b3b495988750bfd6dddd64e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the man ………………………………….. purse was lost?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "acf838d3bf2e4868b3899ae9c8255ed4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met a man …………………………………… had just returned from America.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ac6f21d9bcf4c44a9a6f917fe8dc0d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only he …………………………………. wears the shoe knows where it pinches.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "who",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f26afec4685f43bf99c6c80faf0c42c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ………………………………. my grandfather built.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8bb3521a6b264d789eed2bdc7907d857"
        },
        {
            "question": "The spectators applauded the batsman ……………………………………. performance was spectacular.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a6b888bd93bc4beda9179160236a2957"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………………. the gods love die young.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Which",
                "Whom"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "26ec326a6ce44be4bb01d2dbf99da6a8"
        }
    ]
}